Hello everyone, I will show you how to make a colored pattern.
First, find the pattern material in the window of the picture.
Then apply it to the plate on the collar.
Find the pattern of the pattern material in the attribute container.
Use PS to open.
Use PS to draw the color construction effect.
The purple RGB value is the same as the dark purple in the close.
Fill in its base color.
Then build a new layer to fill in the white.
You can use the marker tool to assist.
Next, save it.
This is the effect of the saved pattern.
In close, replace the original pattern.
You can use the edit pattern tool to adjust the position of the pattern.
If you need to do a three-dimensional construction of the pattern,
We need to make a corresponding call pattern in PS.
Select a layer.
Fill in the black.
Copy the white layer.
And merge the layers.
Add this layer to blur the high-fiber.
This is the high-fiber blur.
This is the effect after the high-fiber blur.
Save it.
After saving, apply this call pattern.
Adjust the call degree to 1.
Adjust the particle diameter to 1.
Turn on render.
Let's see the effect.
As you see, the value will be converted to 1 to 1.
You can see the result here.
Then, you do the same.